export const questions = [
    { question: "How many US states begin with letter P?", choices: ["1", "2", "3", "4"], correctAnswer: "1", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "Austin is the capital of which US state?", choices: ["New Mexico", "Utah", "Georgia", "Texas"], correctAnswer: "Texas", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "In what year was the building of the Brooklyn Bridge completed?", choices: ["1897", "1883", "1910", "1901"], correctAnswer: "1883", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "Which US state borders six states and one Canadian province?", choices: ["Ohio", "Michigan", "Idaho", "N. Dakota"], correctAnswer: "Idaho", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "In the New American Standard Bible, after Uriah's murder, who was the prophet that warned David of his son's death?", choices: ["Nathan", "Samuel", "Isaiah", "Daniel"], correctAnswer: "Nathan", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "What book of the Bible has this verse: And God saw every thing that he had made, and, behold, it was very good.?", choices: ["Joshua", "Exodus", "Genesis", "Jude"], correctAnswer: "Genesis", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "Which book of the Bible tells the story of a young girl that becomes queen and saves the Jews from a horrible villain?", choices: ["Diana", "Esther", "Rahab", "Ruth"], correctAnswer: "Esther", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "What relation is David to Solomon in the Bible?", choices: ["Son", "Brother", "Disciple", "Father"], correctAnswer: "Father", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "In The Bible, Genesis is the first book of the Old Testament, but what is the first book of the New Testament?", choices: ["John", "Micah", "Luke", "Malachi"], correctAnswer: "Malachi", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "Which warrior and former spy is credited with writing a book of the Bible which is also named after him?", choices: ["Joshua", "Samuel", "Daniel", "David"], correctAnswer: "Joshua", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "Which Biblical patriarch passed a night wrestling with an angel?", choices: ["Moses", "Isaac", "Jacob", "Joseph"], correctAnswer: "Isaac", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "Goat Island and Horseshoe Falls are parts of what well-known smooching destination?", choices: ["Disney World", "Niagara Falls", "Alaska", "Appalachian"], correctAnswer: "Niagara Falls", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "Which country is also referred to as 'Hellas'?", choices: ["Italy", "Turkey", "Croatia", "Greece"], correctAnswer: "Greece", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "What country is also known as 'The Land of the Blue Sky'?", choices: ["China", "Mongolia", "Japan", "Tawain"], correctAnswer: "Mongolia", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "Which country in Europe is also known as 'The Boot'?", choices: ["Greece", "Norway", "Italy", "Turkey"], correctAnswer: "Italy", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "What is the only U.S. state to border two oceans?", choices: ["Alaska", "Hawaii", "Florida", "Texas"], correctAnswer: "Alaska", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "The state of Nevada was created out of which large territory that would later become the Bee Hive state?", choices: ["Ohio", "Montana", "Utah", "Idaho"], correctAnswer: "Utah", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "What U.S. state is known as the -Mother of Presidents- because at least eight presidents have been born there?", choices: ["Virginia", "Maryland", "Illinois", "Maine"], correctAnswer: "Virginia", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "How many states in the USA begin with the letter D?", choices: ["4", "2", "1", "3"], correctAnswer: "1", isAnswered: false },
    { question: "Which is the largest country in the Caribbean by area?", choices: ["Haiti", "Belize", "Jamaica", "Cuba"], correctAnswer: "Cuba", isAnswered: false },
];